Guide to the Norman Strung Papers 1966-1982
Montana State University-Bozeman Library
- Magazine Manuscripts, Series 2
  - Confirmed publication manuscripts, Subseries 1
    - "Stretching Your Wader's Life", Field and Stream, May 1973 (Box-folder 16/10)
      p. 24, article and correspondence
    - "Solitude 'Round the Bend", Watersport, May 1973 (Box-folder 16/11)
      p. 26-28, article and correspondence
    - "The Greatest Hatch of Them All", Colorado, May/June 1973 (Box-folder 16/12)
      p. 19R, article and correspondence
    - "Gunstock Survival Kit and Return Address", Sports Afield, June 1973 (Box-folder 16/13)
    - "Head for High Country", Outdoor Life, July 1973 (Box-folder 16/14)
      p. 40
    - "Dam Fishing", Outdoor Life, August 1973 (Box-folder 16/15)
    - "Writing the Magazine Article That Sells Most Often", Outdoors Unlimited, September 1973 (Box-folder 16/16)
      p. 4-5
    - "Reprieve for Broken Rods", Sports Afield, October 1973 (Box-folder 16/17)
      p. 125
    - "Sackcloth and Scaup", Sports Afield, October 1973 (Box-folder 16/18)
      p. 127
    - "Ringnecks in Montana", Outdoor Life, November 1973 (Box-folder 16/19)
      p. 58
    - "The Rare One", Field and Stream, December 1973 (Box-folder 16/20)
      p. 44+, article and correspondence
    - "Goose Hunting", Outdoor Life, December 1973 (Box-folder 16/21)
    - "Campfire control and cooking", Outdoor Cooking Digest, 1974 (Box-folder 16/22)
    - "The Challenge of the Lone Antelope", True's Hunting Yearbook, 1974 (Box-folder 16/23)
      p. 24+, article and correspondence
    - "Beware of the Dog", Sports Afield, January 1974 (Box-folder 16/24)
      p. 84
    - "Help Unwanted", Sports Afield, January 1974 (Box-folder 16/25)
    - "Map Reading", Sports Afield, January 1974 (Box-folder 16/26)
    - "The Bass Capital", Fishing World, January/February 1974 (Box-folder 16/27)
      p. 34+, article and correspondence
    - "Good Month at Hebgen", Outdoor Life, February 1974 (Box-folder 16/28)
      p. 44-45
    - "Doggie Bags", Field and Stream, March 1974 (Box-folder 17/1)
      p. 98-100, article and correspondence
    - "Missouri Float", Outdoor Life, March 1974 (Box-folder 17/2)
      p. 71-72, article and correspondence
    - "A Food for All Seasons", Sports Afield, May 1974 (Box-folder 17/3)
      p. 88
    - "Great American Campsites", Argosy, April 1974 (Box-folder 17/4)
      p. 53-60, article and correspondence
    - "Montana's Early Cure for Fishing Fever", Outdoor Life, April 1974 (Box-folder 17/5)
      p. 67, article and correspondence
    - "A Mossy Debate", Sports Afield, June 1974 (Box-folder 17/6)
      p. 97
    - "Body Measurement", Sports Afield, July 1974 (Box-folder 17/7)
      p. 81-82
    - "Winnepeg's New Wet Lands", Ducks Unlimited, July/August 1974 (Box-folder 17/8)
      p. 34
    - "Warm Weather Ducks", Field and Stream, September 1974 (Box-folder 17/9)
      p. 52
    - "The Water Wolves", Field and Stream, October 1974 (Box-folder 17/10)
      p. 62+, article and correspondence
    - "Quick Camper Removal", Sports Afield, October 1974 (Box-folder 17/11)
      p. 107
    - "The Bow and Big Game", Field and Stream, November 1974 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - "Carpeting the Cobbles", Sports Afield, January 1975 (Box-folder 17/13)
      p. 83, for copy of typed article see Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976
    - "When Ice Will Suffice", Sports Afield, January 1975 (Box-folder 17/14)
      p. 86
    - "Rx for Rafters", Field and Stream, February 1975 (Box-folder 17/15)
      p. 128, article and correspondence
    - "More Tip-ups Allowed", Outdoor Life, February 1975 (Box-folder 17/16)
      p. 31
    - "March on the Madison", Outdoor Life, March 1975 (Box-folder 17/17)
    - "Displaced Trout", Fishing World, March/April 1975 (Box-folder 17/18)
      p. 38, article and correspondence
    - "Spring Snowmobiling for Cutthroat", Outdoor Life, April 1975 (Box-folder 17/19)
      p. 62
    - "The Neglected Western Whitetail", The American Hunter, May 1975 (Box-folder 17/20)
      p. 44
    - "Some Hot Prospects of the Opener", Outdoor Life, May 1975 (Box-folder 17/21)
      p. 41
    - "Bighorn: Great Place for Montana Walleyes", Outdoor Life, June 1975 (Box-folder 17/22)
      p. 39
    - "Centennial" A Grand Place to Camp and Fish", Outdoor Life, July 1975 (Box-folder 17/23)
      p. 37
    - "Keep Your Bottle Under Wraps," Sports Afield, July 1975 (Box-folder 17/24)
      p. 80, for copy of typed article see Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976
    - -----, Outdoor Life, August 1975 (Box-folder 17/25)
    - "Gunslinging", Field and Stream, September 1975 (Box-folder 17/26)
      p. 112+, article and correspondence
    - "Tricks that Fool Trout in Montana Right Now", Outdoor Life, September 1975 (Box-folder 17/27)
      p. 41, article and correspondence
    - "Mountain Medicine", Sports Afield, September 1975 (Box-folder 17/28)
      p. 108
    - "Thoughts on Freshwater Trolling", Fishing World, September/October 1975 (Box-folder 17/29)
      p. 22
    - "The Eyes Have It", Field and Stream, October 1975 (Box-folder 17/30)
      p. 84, article and correspondence
    - "Montana Deer Hunters Face Mixed Prospects", Outdoor Life, November 1975 (Box-folder 17/31)
    - "Learning the Ropes", Sports Afield, November 1975 (Box-folder 17/32)
      p. 93
    - "Montana: Where to get a goose for Christmas", Outdoor Life, December 1975 (Box-folder 17/33)
      p. 45
    - "Certain Smell", Sports Afield, December 1975 (Box-folder 17/34)
      p. 90
    - "Decoys for a Dime", Sports Afield, December 1975 (Box-folder 17/35)
    - "Fast Feathers", Sports Afield, December 1975 (Box-folder 17/36)
      p. 89
    - "Fishing for Better Hunting", Sports Afield, December 1975 (Box-folder 17/37)
    - "Get Big Vacation Trout", Fawcett's Fishing Journal, n. 1, 1976 (Box-folder 17/38)
      p. 19
    - "The Happy Hooker", Sports Afield Fishing Annual, 1976 (Box-folder 17/39)
    - "Are You Walking On Thin Ice?", Boy's Life, January 1976 (Box-folder 17/40)
      p. 54
    - "Blessed by the Broad Broadbill", Field and Stream, January 1976 (Box-folder 17/41)
      p. 60
    - "The Great Whitetail Hang-up", Field and Stream, January 1976 (Box-folder 18/1)
      p. 68
    - "Court Bouillion and Fish Tracts", Sports Afield, January 1976 (Box-folder 18/2)
    - "Nets to You", Sports Afield, January 1976 (Box-folder 18/3)
    - "An Old Trick for New Tracts", Sports Afield, January 1976 (Box-folder 18/4)
      p. 85
    - "Scout Knife Knowhow", Boy's Life, February 1976 (Box-folder 18/5)
      p. 71
    - "The Tales Tracks Tell", Boy's Life, February 1976 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - "Try Outwitting Coyotes in Montana this month", Outdoor Life, February 1976 (Box-folder 18/7)
      p. 29
    - "How to Sharpen a Knife when You Can't Sharpen a Knife", Sports Afield, February 1976 (Box-folder 18/8)
      p. 114
    - "A Tale of Three Trophies", Deer Sportsman, March 1976 (Box-folder 18/9)
      p. 16, article and correspondence
    - "Getting a Handle on Your Outboard", Sports Afield, March 1976 (Box-folder 18/10)
      p. 94
    - "What Makes the Worm Turn?", Sports Afield, April 1976 (Box-folder 18/11)
      p. 128
    - "Trout Opener", Outdoor Life, May 1976 (Box-folder 18/12)
    - "Masking Your Mug", Sports Afield, May 1976 (Box-folder 18/13)
      p. 124
    - "A Tired Moose", Sports Afield, May 1976 (Box-folder 18/14)
      p. 122
    - "Three Sails by the Sunset", Gray's Sporting Journal (Trophy Fishing), Summer 1976 (Box-folder 18/15)
      p. 64, article and correspondence
    - "A Good Time to Floatfish for Trout in Montana", Outdoor Life, August 1976 (Box-folder 18/16)
    - "Expect Fine Gunning for Grouse in Montana", Outdoor Life, September 1976 (Box-folder 18/17)
    - "A Helping Hand", Sports Afield, September 1976 (Box-folder 18/18)
      p. 102
    - "Try a Beer-B-Cue", Sports Afield, September 1976 (Box-folder 18/19)
      p. 105
    - "Two in One Campfire", Sports Afield, September 1976 (Box-folder 18/20)
      p. 103
    - "Hunting the High Plains", Gray's Sporting Journal (Upland Birds), Fall 1976 (Box-folder 18/21)
    - "Ode to Billy Joe", Gray's Sporting Journal (Big Game), Fall 1976 (Box-folder 18/22)
      p. 71, article and correspondence
    - "Bucks by Barometer", Fawcett's Hunting Journal, October 1976 (Box-folder 18/23)
    - "Suburban Bucks", Field and Stream, October 1976 (Box-folder 18/24)
    - -----, Outdoor Life, October 1976 (Box-folder 18/25)
    - "Appointment in Culiacan", Gray's Sporting Journal (Waterfowl), November 1976 (Box-folder 18/26)
    - "The Once and Future Elk Hunt", Field and Stream, November 1976 (Box-folder 18/27)
      p. 56, article and correspondence
    - "The Dollar Duck Dog", Sports Afield, November 1976 (Box-folder 18/28)
      p. 101
    - "Where and How to Hunt Whitetails in Montana", Outdoor Life, November 1976 (Box-folder 18/29)
      p. 42
    - "Drafty Deer Skinning", Sports Afield, December 1976 (Box-folder 18/30)
      p. 92
    - "Getting Unstuck", Sports Afield, December 1976 (Box-folder 18/31)
      p. 95
    - -----, Outdoor Life, December 1976 (Box-folder 18/32)
    - "Boot Break-in", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/33)
      p. 4
    - "Campfire Smoke House", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/34)
      p. 8
    - "Carpeting the Cobbles, Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/35)
      p. 7
    - "Firewater", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/36)
    - "Hook Sharpening", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/37)
      p. 55
    - "How to be a Successful Fly Catcher", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/38)
      p. 13
    - "Keep Your Bottle Under Wraps", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/39)
      p. 66
    - "Point of Interest", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/40)
      p. 87
    - "Simple Smoking", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/41)
      p. 112
    - "Tacklebox House Cleaning", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/42)
      p. 14
    - "Tender Trap", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/43)
    - "The Thumb Dial", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/44)
      p. 116
    - "What Once Sewed So Shall Ye Reap", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/45)
    - "Yes We Have No Bandannas", Sports Afield Outdoor Almanac, 1976 (Box-folder 18/46)
      p. 27
    - "The Arrow Points the Way", Field and Stream Hunting Annual, 1977 (Box-folder 18/47)
    - "A Scattergunner's Secret: Boot Your Butt", Sports Afield, January 1977 (Box-folder 18/48)
    - "South of the Border on a Shoestring", Field and Stream, February 1977 (Box-folder 18/49)
      p. 158, article and correspondence
    - "Cure for Cabin Fever: A Big Mountain Rainbow", Outdoor Life, March 1977 (Box-folder 19/1)
      p. 43
    - "Outboard First Aid", Sports Afield, March 1977 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - "Montana's Underfished Bass: Plunk a Plug Here", Outdoor Life, April 1977 (Box-folder 19/3)
      p. 43-44
    - "A Great Grate", Sports Afield, April 1977 (Box-folder 19/4)
      p. 117
    - "New Theory on Carcass Care", Sports Afield, April 1977 (Box-folder 19/5)
      p. 121
    - "Rafting Montana's Blackfoot River", Exploring, April 1977 (Box-folder 19/6)
    - "Getting Started: Beaver Ponds", Fawcett's Fishing Journal, Spring 1977 (Box-folder 19/7)
      p. 66, article and correspondence
    - "Float Trip Camping", Field and Stream, May 1977 (Box-folder 19/8)
    - "The Perils of Adopting a Deer", Sports Afield, May 1977 (Box-folder 19/9)
      p. 119
    - "Woodland Bison: World's Rarest Trophy", Sports Afield, May 1977 (Box-folder 19/10)
      p. 44, published under name of Walter Cook
    - "The Pitter-Patter Principle (rain is catching time)", Outdoor Life, May 1977 (Box-folder 19/11)
      p. 96, article and correspondence
    - "A State of Mind (Pothole bass and pike)", Gray's Sporting Journal, May/June 1977 (Box-folder 19/12)
      p. 80, article and correspondence
    - "Trout-time of the Push Root", Field and Stream, June 1977 (Box-folder 19/13)
    - "Superfly", Outdoor Life, June 1977 (Box-folder 19/14)
    - "Art of Finding Arrowheads", Sports Afield, June 1977 (Box-folder 19/15)
    - "Blue Ribbon Float Trip", Boy's Life, July 1977 (Box-folder 19/16)
      p. 8, article and correspondence
    - "Say Hello to a Big Dolly on the Flathead", Outdoor Life, July 1977 (Box-folder 19/17)
      p. 29, no article only correspondence
    - "Juice of Jewelweed", Sports Afield, July 1977 (Box-folder 19/18)
    - "Float the Blackfoot for Trout and Tranquility", Outdoor Life, August 1977 (Box-folder 19/19)
    - "The Endless Fall", Field and Stream, September 1977 (Box-folder 19/20)
      p. 76
    - "Deer Hunting Prospects Look Good in Montana", Outdoor Life, September 1977 (Box-folder 19/21)
      p. 51
    - "The Foxy Pheasant", Field and Stream, October 1977 (Box-folder 19/22)
      p. 42, article and correspondence
    - "The Bright Promise of Montana Elk Hunting", Outdoor Life, October 1977 (Box-folder 19/23)
    - "Hunting Sharptail Grouse", Field and Stream, November 1977 (Box-folder 19/24)
      p. 88A
    - "Whitetails and Wild Tales", Field and Stream, November 1977 (Box-folder 19/25)
      p 42
    - "Pheasant Season may be one of Montana's Best", Outdoor Life, November 1977 (Box-folder 19/26)
    - "Game Stringers", Sports Afield, November 1977 (Box-folder 19/27)
    - "Montana Spring Creeks Tops for Mallards", Outdoor Life, December 1977 (Box-folder 19/28)
    - "Anatomy of a Duck Marsh", Sports Afield, December 1977 (Box-folder 19/29)
    - "Float Hunting" Baker Deer Hunting Annual, 1978 (Box-folder 19/30)
      p. 20, article and correspondence
    - "Finding It", Gray's Sporting Journal, Winter 1978 (Box-folder 19/31)
      p. 21
    - "Goose Hunting Basics", Field and Stream, January 1978 (Box-folder 19/32)
    - "It's Canepole Time on Montana Rivers", Outdoor Life, February 1978 (Box-folder 19/33)
    - "For Those Who Wait", Sports Afield, February 1978 (Box-folder 19/34)
    - "Bait up for Spring", Outdoor Life, March 1978 (Box-folder 19/35)
      p. 74, article and correspondence
    - "The Prince of the Prairies", Sports Afield, March 1978 (Box-folder 19/36)
      p. 58, article and correspondence
    - "New Maps: The Key that Unlocks Public Lands", Sports Afield, June 1978 (Box-folder 19/37)
      p. 72
    - "Danger at Dawn", Sports Afield, July 1978 (Box-folder 19/38)
      p. 70
    - "Western High Plains Varminting Favorite: The Prairie Dog", Sports Afield, July 1978 (Box-folder 19/39)
      p. 46
    - "Bitter is Better", Field and Stream, October 1978 (Box-folder 19/40)
      p. 87A, article and correspondence
    - "Mule Deer Are Smarter", Field and Stream, October 1978 (Box-folder 19/41)
      p. 98, article and correspondence
    - "The Jigs up in Fresh or Salt Water", Sports Afield, October 1978 (Box-folder 19/42)
    - "No-slide Gunslin", Sports Afield, December 1978 (Box-folder 19/43)
    - "For Trophy Hunters Only", Field and Stream: Deer Hunting, 1979 (Box-folder 19/44)
      p. 4-7
    - "Mulies of the Iron Jaws", Hunter's Bible, Edwin Bauer - editor, 1979 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - "Rafting - West, White and Wild", Outdoor Annual, 1979 (Box-folder 20/2)
      p. 19-20, article and correspondence
    - "How to Flag Wave Ducks to Your Dekes", Scotch Game Call: Hunting, 1979 (Box-folder 20/3)
      p. 20-23
    - "Decoy Sets that really pull", Sports Afield: Hunting Annual, 1979 (Box-folder 20/4)
      p. 70+
    - "Longer Wader Life", Sports Afield, January 1979 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - "Bull Elk with a Bow in Montana", Sports Afield, January 1979 (Box-folder 20/6)
      p. 48, no article only correspondence
    - "Snook Heaven: Mexico's Pacific Coast", Fishing World, January/February 1979 (Box-folder 20/7)
      p. 14+
    - "Shades of Brown", Field and Stream, February 1979 (Box-folder 20/8)
      p. 47+
    - "Mexican Bobwhites", Sports Afield, February 1979 (Box-folder 20/9)
      p. 42, no article only correspondence
    - "Charm 'em with Silver and Gold", Outdoor Life, March 1979 (Box-folder 20/10)
      p. 80+, article and correspondence
    - "Mighty Montana Man", Sports Afield, March 1979 (Box-folder 20/11)
      p. 88, article and correspondence
    - "Chasing Rainbows", Field and Stream, April 1979 (Box-folder 20/12)
      p. D-E
    - "The Lure of Fly-Fishing Lakes", Field and Stream, April 1979 (Box-folder 20/13)
      p. 112-118
    - "The Rites of Spring", Field and Stream, May 1979 (Box-folder 20/14)
    - "Questions Answered on Travel in Mexico", Sports Afield, May 1979 (Box-folder 20/15)
      p. 44, no article only correspondence
    - "Woodland Bison, World's Rarest Trophy", Sports Afield, May 1979 (Box-folder 20/16)
    - "Bison in Poland", Safari, May/June 1979 (Box-folder 20/17)
      p. 42-45+, written under name of Walter Cook, no article only correspondence
    - "Exotic Fishing Trips on Tap in Amazon", Sports Afield, June 1979 (Box-folder 20/18)
    - "Shoot Driven Birds on Long Island Now", Sports Afield, July 1979 (Box-folder 20/19)
      p. 100
    - "The Gulphers - Trout in Lake Shallows", Field and Stream, August 1979 (Box-folder 20/20)
      p. A-C, article and correspondence
    - "Big Apple Bird Hunting Season", Sports Afield, September 1979 (Box-folder 20/21)
      p. 38
    - "Elk Low Down", Field and Stream, October 1979 (Box-folder 20/22)
      p. 60+, article and correspondence
    - "How to Hunt Spooked Mulies", Field and Stream, October 1979 (Box-folder 20/23)
      p. 48+, article and correspondence
    - "The Inside Track", Outdoor Life, October 1979 (Box-folder 20/24)
    - "Cement Decoy Weights", Sports Afield, October 1979 (Box-folder 20/25)
    - "The Game Bird You Always Miss: Snipe", Sports Afield, October 1979 (Box-folder 20/26)
    - "Trout Heavyweights", Field and Stream, November 1979 (Box-folder 20/27)
    - "Wing and Fin time for Outdoorsman", Mechanix Illustrated, November 1979 (Box-folder 20/28)
      p. 98+, article and correspondence
    - "Fine Bird Shooting in the British Isles", Sports Afield, November 1979 (Box-folder 20/29)
    - "Gold in Old Lures", Sports Afield, November 1979 (Box-folder 20/30)
      p. 78, article and correspondence
    - "Scots Offer Salmon Fishing in Style", Sports Afield, November 1979 (Box-folder 20/31)
    - "Sturdier Gun Racks", Sports Afield, November 1979 (Box-folder 20/32)
    - "A Dog's Security Blanket", Sports Afield, December 1979 (Box-folder 20/33)
      p. 76, no article only correspondence
    - "How to Read to Read a River Coleman Wide World of Canoeing, 1980 (Box-folder 20/34)
      p.52-61
    - "Knives are better than ever", Guttman: Knife Annual, 1980 (Box-folder 20/35)
      p. 18-20
    - "Quote this carefully", Sports Afield, December 1979 (Box-folder 20/36)
      p. 80
    - "Packing Out", Sports Afield: Deer, 1980 (Box-folder 20/37)
      p. 72-75, article and correspondence
    - "The Snowbird", Field and Stream, February 1980 (Box-folder 20/38)
    - "The Fish That Took Over Winter", Mechanix Illustrated, February 1980 (Box-folder 20/39)
    - "Bargain Prices in Maine Wilderness", Sports Afield, February 1980 (Box-folder 20/40)
      p. 50
    - "Opening Day at Bubbles Falls", Sports Afield, February 1980 (Box-folder 20/41)
    - "Strange Limit", Sports Afield, February 1980 (Box-folder 20/42)
    - "Midday Trout", Field and Stream, March 1980 (Box-folder 21/1)
    - "Three States Offer Limited Swan Hunts", Sports Afield, March 1980 (Box-folder 21/2)
    - "Wise up to Whitefish", Outdoor Life, March 1980 (Box-folder 21/3)
      p. 81+
    - "How to build a better trout stream", Mechanix Illustrated, April 1980 (Box-folder 21/4)
      p. 15+
    - "Trout before Runoff", Outdoor Life, April 1980 (Box-folder 21/5)
      p. 62+
    - "Wave Danger", Sports Afield, April 1980 (Box-folder 21/6)
      p. 126
    - "Worn Waders", Sports Afield, April 1980 (Box-folder 21/7)
      p. 127, no article only correspondence
    - "Montana Nobody Knows", Field and Stream, May 1980 (Box-folder 21/8)
      p. D-E, article and correspondence
    - "Traveling Light", Field and Stream, May 1980 (Box-folder 21/9)
      p. 94+
    - "Outdoors: How to make a fishing rod travel", Mechanix Illustrated, May 1980 (Box-folder 21/10)
    - "Manicures many cures", Sports Afield, May 1980 (Box-folder 21/11)
      p. 96
    - "Things that go bump on your outboard", Mechanix Illustrated, June 1980 (Box-folder 21/12)
      p. 2+
    - "Field Guide: Tarp Tips", Outdoor Life, June 1980 (Box-folder 21/13)
      p. 109-110
    - "Big-Game Bargain Found in Scotland", Sports Afield, June 1980 (Box-folder 21/14)
    - "Floating for trout", Field and Stream, August 1980 (Box-folder 21/15)
    - "Roughing It: The safe way to fell a tree", Mechanix Illustrated, September 1980 (Box-folder 21/16)
      p. 104
    - "Roughing It: Wheels in the woods", Mechanix Illustrated, October 1980 (Box-folder 21/17)
    - "Offbeat rabbit hunting in Great Britain", Sports Afield, October 1980 (Box-folder 21/18)
    - "Buck Fever", Field and Stream, November 1980 (Box-folder 21/19)
      p. 50+, article and correspondence
    - "Finding the right rifle", Field and Stream, November 1980 (Box-folder 21/20)
      p. 78+
    - "Roughing It: Putting the heat on", Mechanix Illustrated, November 1980 (Box-folder 21/21)
      p. 24+
    - "Sport with Late Season Elk", Field and Stream, December 1980 (Box-folder 21/22)
    - "Trout Windfall", Field and Stream, December 1980 (Box-folder 21/23)
    - "Roughing It: Your own t(r)oll bridge", Mechanix Illustrated, December 1980 (Box-folder 21/24)
      p. 22+
    - "Bayman's Solstice", Gray's Sporting Journal, Fall 1980 (Box-folder 21/25)
      p. 28-41
    - "Roughing It: Barn board basics", Mechanix Illustrated, January 1981 (Box-folder 21/26)
      p. 16
    - "Roughing It: Getting the jump on spring", Mechanix Illustrated, February 1981 (Box-folder 21/27)
    - "Roughing It: Recycling old oil", Mechanix illustrated, March 1981 (Box-folder 21/28)
      p. 32+
    - "Australia overrun with game animals", Sports Afield, March 1981 (Box-folder 21/29)
    - "Mixed game bag offered in Montana", Sports Afield, March 1981 (Box-folder 21/30)
    - "Fishing for Mountain Trout", Backpacker, Spring 1981 (Box-folder 21/31)
    - "Roughing It: A moveable utility shed", Mechanix Illustrated, April 1981 (Box-folder 21/32)
    - "Trout Nymphing - Naturally", Outdoor Life, April 1981 (Box-folder 21/33)
      p. 72+
    - "Bonus Gesse", Field and Stream, May 1981 (Box-folder 21/34)
    - "Troll for Ice-out Trout", Field and Stream, May 1981 (Box-folder 21/35)
      p. A-C
    - "Roughing It: Getting wood cheap", Mechanix Illustrated, May 1981 (Box-folder 21/36)
      p. 30+
    - "Direct Flight to Saskatchewan Lodge", Sports Afield, May 1981 (Box-folder 21/37)
    - "Gesse inundate Long Island, New York", Sports Afield, May 1981 (Box-folder 21/38)
    - "Ponds of Plenty", Field and Stream, June 1981 (Box-folder 21/39)
      p. A-X, article and correspondence
    - "Roughing It: Build your own smokehouse", Mechanix Illustrated, June 1981 (Box-folder 21/40)
      p. 38+
    - "Beaverhead's Big Eaters", Field and Stream, July 1981 (Box-folder 21/41)
    - "Roughing It: Building it with logs", Mechanix Illustrated, July 1981 (Box-folder 21/42)
    - "Summer Trout Secrets", Field and Stream, August 1981 (Box-folder 21/43)
    - "Roughing It: Tabletops from scrap hardwood", Mechanix Illustrated, August 1981 (Box-folder 21/44)
    - "Banner year for Montana's big game", Sports Afield, August 1981 (Box-folder 21/45)
      p. 40, article and correspondence
    - "Jiggerbobbin for Bass", Field and Stream, September 1981 (Box-folder 21/46)
    - "The 'Ranch Hunt' Option", Field and Stream, September 1981 (Box-folder 21/47)